you'd be surprised how long it takes
to make
about a hundred
floating glass rings
this is what i've spent the last day
making and not only making it but making
it perfectly symmetrical
for my mini game
so check it out it is 100
finished the last thing i need to do
is test it myself
i'm not sure how this is going to go i
thought about the design very carefully
if you look over this side meaning that
when both participants jump out each
side of the airplane they have a 100
fair game so here's how it goes the
yellow rings are the biggest the orange
rings are the second biggest and the red
is tiny and they will all be worth
different amounts of points so now let's
just see how this goes so the idea is to
go through as many hoops as possible and
there's a bonus for the first person who
makes it to the bottom
of course
it's very very possible that you will
die
as you hit one of the glass panes if
this happens you still get your points
but obviously if you die you miss out on
all the ones ahead of you so
jump in
it's very easy to die it's very easy to
die
okay let's try again
right yellow
i don't even know if i went through that
and
okay so if you take it safe
if you take it nice and safe you can get
some decent points where did my elytra
go and how do i get out oh no
i didn't make a way out
i don't have any rockets
help
[Music]
i'm stuck in a hole of my own creation
they're there
okay so let's try this again and see if
the best what the best score is
so let's try this again and let's try
and aim for the best score i need to
work out how plausible it is to get
through
some of the more
diffic
not very plausible
gotta take some risks
here we go
orange
orange yellow
yellow
nailed it
so i think the red hoops should be worth
a lot of points the yellow just one
because they are the easiest and then
the orange should be worth two
and then five maybe even more bonus
points for being the first to reach the
bottom
because what we don't want them to do is
this which is where they go so slowly
that they just get managed to get
through
every single one although having said
that i can get through so many okay we
need a a really big bonus point for
being the first to get to the bottom
because otherwise
floating through here very slowly
that's uh
that's the easy way out that is not what
i want so i'm getting a pretty good idea
of what i need to happen here all i need
to do now is get all i need to do now is
get hold of b dubs and impulse who are
the two contestants for my
mini aim so let's give this another go
shall we cause i reckon i reckon we
could do pretty well if we
just whoa we got a red one
oh that was pretty good that was pretty
good here's the other problem i cannot
keep track of my own score
while flying through these rings so
i'm actually gonna have to replay mod
all three of these
and count them afterwards like like a
full-on replay to assess who wins but
this has ended up being such a cool
little mini game honestly it is
challenging and i'm a sucker for any
flying mini games so i'm thinking
three rounds each
and we take the best score or
three rounds each and we take
an average of the three either way the
math spit will come way after
so let's get b dubs and impulse together
i'll give them both a practice round so
they can kind of get to grips with how
to play this
whoa
oh no i thought it was gonna nail it
of course what they could do is just not
aim for any at all and just be the first
to get to the bottom
but then
they miss out on the rings so hopefully
this will be balanced enough that they
make those decisions
okay let's make a scoreboard
and see how this goes
welcome contestants to green skydive i
should have come up with a better name
rings of death is a suitable name
yeah oh no that's scary though i like
the sound of that i have been replacing
these rings all day and
i hope this goes well so if you if i can
draw your attention to this pillar here
this shows you the points so you're both
going to be jumping out of the plane up
there and trying to fly through as many
hoops as possible making your way down
to the water below so red is five points
orange is two and yellow which is the
biggest one is one point and it is a
race you are both jumping out the plane
at the same time the first one to get to
the bottom gets 12 whole points which is
a lot it's a it's a big deal to get to
the bottom first
but you must go through at least two
hoops to qualify for that twelve oh man
those red ones are really tiny they are
really small they are oh my gosh five
blocks
wide oh
you've gotta be perfect on them they are
worth five points so two of those and
you probably will get the win
are you ready to go i'm thinking three
rounds each at the same time and the
average score will be declared the
winner of my mini-game i'm gonna give
you guys a couple of practice runs
because it's very unfair for you to just
go into this blind okay okay thank you
because i'm super nervous
yes
first challenge is to fly up to the the
plane and get inside
i made it this doesn't bode well does it
i'm gonna
[Applause]
couple of shulker boxes here with elytra
and rockets if you want to put all of
your stuff in here because it it goes ka
splat and goes everywhere and we don't
oh okay
this is gonna be practice though right
yeah this is this is just practice all
right okay are you guys ready
my heart is in my throat practice round
let's see if you both survive on three
two
one jump
oh here we go
oh my gosh the first ring
what he just made it
and i made it that was over very fast
this is the real deal no more test runs
oh gosh i'm nervous
how did your smile looks like a nervous
smile beat ups it's a it's a fierce
smile yeah the one
up on the side that's what i should have
put in the skin okay
okay and you're gonna go you're gonna go
on my uh on jump okay so three
two
one
jump
oh there's a little pause there that you
did i didn't like the pause action
um oh oh oh oh oh oh oh no he's faster
than me
oh b-dubs
i think you beat me but i did go through
a couple rings you did get a couple
rings i got a couple as well i got three
i think oh no if you beat me down here
then you probably won that one oh no
i would like to propose game master i
would like to propose a an additional
wager if possible
between you and impulse
impulse
just after you win round one
impulse and i are co-owners of lamps
plus in town
winner
gets all the profits for one month
okay wow
he said it you heard me
okay
even though you got a lead on me round
one
[Music]
dubs didn't even fly he just fell
i pranked that that was my
fault
falling with style yes
i did it's gotta be pretty close this is
this is probably gonna make or break it
because i think it's gonna come down to
this
last jump
three
two
one
jump
oh i think i just lost all my
man
king
oh man i'm coming down there with no
electra green you're commenting
oh no you're supposed to say you're this
should be unbiased he was rooting for me
he
okay right i think we still we still
better do
the scores properly
just in case so you're gonna have me
give me give me ten minutes i'm gonna
tot up the scores and we'll meet back at
the at the scoreboard oh come on okay
really
oh geez really you prepared that rub it
in white aren't you i'm wearing a new
outgoing win
[Laughter]
pretty you're wearing victory glasses we
already know who won because
impulse failed the resistance quite
spectacular i'm so sorry i hit the
second ring out of the plane i just
think it's stuff the final scores are in
after
reviewing the replay mod and you know
what even if i'm a couple of points off
it was actually quite difficult to
review the winner is hep hep have taken
the first win
the turf war battle i'm sorry i let us
down he's so smug look at his face
to to be fair though
in watching the replay we did notice you
barely got through that second hoop on
the last fraud before you barely
followed the rules i played the system
all right well gg well done if you come
over to my extremely extravagant
winner loser scoreboard over here i'll
let you do the honors b-dubs you can put
a put a lever on the back side of that
and uh on the hip side there you go go
on
light one up
here we go three two one bang
you missed it
are you that bad at red stuff
it's right here
if you want me yeah
this might be a little archaic green we
might want to spruce this up with some
redstone
yeah i mean i had like two seconds to
put this together i think it's a
it's good enough all right
first point officially goes to hep we've
got catching up to do
i realize that all we've done this
episode
is jump out of planes and die what do
you expect from hermitcraft but i also
have some very bad news so not only did
we lose the greens game ring of death
hep have got one point
they've got two points unfortunately xb
went head to head with cub
and we're two nil down
two nil down we have zero points this is
not looking good for the resistance and
i really
really don't want to have to be the one
to fix the mess that i myself made
it's not how we do however i still have
faith but what i need to tell you is
that there are a lot of mini games that
still need to get what the
whoa
sky you're a madman
look at that
this is mighty impressive okay so what i
needed to tell you is that there are
still many mini games that need to get
played and it is a nightmare trying to
arrange mini games and recording with
over 10 people
so
it's going to be over a couple of
episodes we've already got a couple of
games out of the way but we won't know
who wins until much later in the week
and i myself i'm playing in a few of
these mini games later in the week so
hopefully we can bring back a couple of
points for the resistance i'm uh i think
i'm playing in this game the the trident
one in the eighth hole
and i think i'm playing in another one
but i actually can't remember which one
it is uh this one and maybe another one
oh yeah floatage it's gonna be a lot of
fun but for now
i need to leave now on the hermitcraft
server lots of things go on all the time
and you're not always recording
or at least you're not recording
properly so
here's something that happened a couple
of days ago
that i have to tell you about because
it's very very important so i was just
skedaddling around like i normally do
zip zipping flying around and i saw
scar
and he was just i don't know i just sort
of interacted with him i was taking a
look around and then he placed
a baby yoda head
on the floor now i believe that scar is
the biggest fan of baby yoda and i saw
an opportunity and i took it
he then chased me down of course i
kidnapped
his favorite
baby boy in the whole wide world
and i managed to get away with it by
hiding in a trench so if scar wants this
little baby boy back he's gonna have to
go full mando on me and take it back
himself
oh this is gonna be fun
he will do anything to get this little
guy back i think we should just keep
this just in case we happen to lose
because i mean it's not looking good is
it for the war so we'll see this could
be a pretty good
asset but baby yoda memes aside we have
got to do
finally some work in the base now i
talked about this a couple of episodes
ago about how i have got this space
prepared
for a blibby blobby slime farm that's
what they're called that's the technical
redstone name blibby blobby
and i think i know exactly what i need
to do
to get this thing made so time to make
this thing a little bit more productive
and start building it so without further
ado
let's
get into it
[Music]
and we have one side complete
the issue is
the rates are not too great
you see it's not the fact that there
isn't a second one here but i'm not
gonna build a second one before i can
prove that this one works effectively
and so far
it has not produced a lot of slime i've
been afk for a little while
and it's not really
done what it's promised now there's two
big reasons for this one of them
is that the mob cap
is being sucked up by not just me but
everyone on the server and i have a mob
farm
right next to it and this thing is also
running and we'll be using up a lot of
the spawns however
it should still produce a decent amount
of slime
so that leads me to think the only real
reason is that there's a lot of caves
not lit up
all around here
which
this late in the game in the hermitcraft
season it's just a more of a pain than
anything else
however it can't be a bad idea
to go and have a look and see what i can
find
and see if the rates improve at all
you know there wasn't actually that many
caves around here
and the rates
haven't improved a lot but maybe a
little bit just a small amount so i
think this is one of those passive farms
that will just do well in the long run i
have just received a message
from none other
than father christmas tango himself
that it was my day
on the advent calendar yesterday so i
need to head back over to the shopping
district which i only checked out the
other day and open up a present why did
i i'm so used to going to the shopping
district i didn't even think that i
wasn't supposed to be here the portal's
not behind me here we are it feels so
wrong to be getting a present
this early on
i was number
fourteen there i am green i think i was
maybe supposed to check because i'm
definitely late so what do i do do i
break into it
who is this grain character
okay what have we got what have we got
inside our present
[Music]
holy moly potions of slow falling that
didn't quite rhyme but you got the gist
of it what have we got
slow falling and emeralds
and oh
these are the potions that dreams are
made of
oh thank you tango this is
absolutely amazing best christmas
ever i am going to thoroughly enjoy this
because the potion of slow falling
when you're flying is the best thing
ever you can't you can't fall down very
fast you can't skydive very well but
what i love about it
is that if you manage to turn in just
the right way you can float
in mid air
like
really float
you just go down so slowly
for some reason i'm flickering in and
out of existence
mr stark i don't feel so good
there goes i'm firmly back in reality
now but how cool is this discovered that
in season six now if you've made it to
this part of the video not only are you
the most beautiful slash handsome and
amazing person that's ever walked this
planet i have a little i have a little
request for you
so as i said earlier i've got
little baby yoda here and scar will do
just about anything so all i need you to
do
is to let him know
that he can get baby yoda back fair and
square easy peasy all he's got to do is
go up into my plane right here
and baby yoda
will be sitting
driving the plane backwards nope baby
yoda will be driving the plane right
here so if sky wants it back all you got
to do is tell him baby yoda is right
here so with that out of the way how on
earth did you get there get snakes on a
plane
so with that being said that is all we
have time for today in today's episode i
really hope people give this a go and
see what scores they can get
and
we will be playing the rest of the turf
war minigames very very soon and i'm
super excited
it's still two nil as of the end of this
episode
so i hope i really hope
that we win
so thank you very much for watching and
i shall see you in the next episode
good bye
you